<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<cheatsheet title="XML Verification">
   <intro href="/org.eclipse.wst.xml.security.doc/plugin/verify.html">
      <description>
         Welcome to the XML Verification tutorial of the XML-Security Plug-In.<br/>
This tutorial will show you step by step how to verify a signature in a signed XML document using the Verification. You will open a signed XML document and then verify all contained signatures in this document. To start this verification session click the &apos;Click to Begin&apos; link below.<br/>
By the way, this tutorial shows only some possibilities of the XML Digital Signature Verification. You can find more information in the extensive German online help and on the home page of the XML-Security Plug-In.
      </description>
   </intro>
   <item title="Open a signed XML document" dialog="true" skip="true" href="/org.eclipse.platform.doc.user/tasks/tasks-46.htm">
      <description>
         Open an XML document containing at least one digital signature (you may have created with the XML Digital Signature Wizard). You can skip this item if your signed XML document is already opened in an editor.
      </description>
   </item>
   <item title="Verify the digital signatures" dialog="true" skip="false" href="/org.eclipse.wst.xml.security.doc/plugin/verify_view.html">
      <description>
         Start the XML Verification by clicking on &apos;New Verification...&apos; in the context menu &apos;XML Security&apos;. A new view &apos;Signature Verification&apos; appears containing various numbers of entries (depending on the amount of digital signatures in your XML document).<br/>
The color of the entry shows the verification result:<br/>
green indicates a valid signature, red an invalid. Yellow means that it was impossible to verify the signature. You can show additional information on the selected signature by selecting the corresponding signature and clicking on the button &apos;Properties&apos;.
      </description>
   </item>
</cheatsheet>
